第 7 章：弱化音。非重读词有弱化元音。语调的另一面：
Chapter 7 – Reduced Sounds Unstressed words have reduced vowels. The Downside of
弱化音，是嘴唇、舌头、下巴和喉咙动作减少时产生的额外声音。
Intonation Reduced sounds are all those extra sounds created by an absence of lip,
它们是语调的主要功能之一，也真正体现了
tongue, jaw, and throat movement. They're a principal function of intonation and are
美式声音的特征。弱化音就是谷。美式
truly indicative of the American sound. Reduced sounds are valleys. American
语调由峰和谷、阶梯顶部和底部组成。
intonation is made up of peaks and valleys, tops of staircases, and bottoms
要有强峰，就必须发展出深谷。
of staircases. To have strong peaks, you'll have to develop deep valleys. These
深谷应该填入各种弱化元音，
deep valleys should be filled with all kinds of reduced vowels, one in
特别是完全中性的 schwa。忽略拼写，因为你很可能一开始
particular, the completely neutral schwa. Ignore spelling. Since you probably first
通过印刷文字认识英语，所以这会是一个相当大的
became acquainted with English through the printed word, this is going to be quite a
音节位置比拼写更重要。
challenge. The position of a syllable is more important than spelling as an
它更能提示正确发音。例如，photograph 和 photography 这两个词，
indication of correct pronunciation. For example, the words photograph and
各有两个 O 和一个 A。第一个词的重音落在第一个
photography each have two O's and an A. The first word is stressed on the first
音节，所以 photograph 听起来就是 photograph。第二个词的重音落在
syllable, so photograph sounds like photograph. The second word is stressed on
第二音节 photography，所以读出来就是 photography。由此可见，
the second syllable, photography, so the word comes out photography. You can see
它们的拼写并不会告诉你它们听起来是什么样。
here that their spelling doesn't tell you how they sound. Word stress or intonation
词重音或语调会决定发音。听词时，要专注于听
will determine the pronunciation. Listening to words. Concentrate on hearing
纯声音，而不是试图让这个词贴合熟悉的拼写。
the pure sounds, not trying to make the word fit a familiar spelling. Otherwise,
你就会绕远路，也会给自己增加很多额外工作和口音。
you'll be taking the long way around and giving yourself both a lot of extra work
带重音、位于峰顶或阶梯顶部的音节是强音节；
and an accent. Syllables that are perched atop a peak or a staircase are strong
也就是说，它们保持原来的发音。
sounds. That is, they maintain their original pronunciation. On the other hand,
落在谷里或较低阶梯上的音节是弱音节，因此
syllables that fall in the valleys or on a lower stair step are weak sounds, thus
有些元音会完全弱化为 schwa，也就是一种非常放松的元音。
they're reduced. Some vowels are reduced completely to schwas, a very relaxed
声音，另一些只是被压低。在下面的练习中，我们将
sound, while others are only toned down. In the following exercises, we'll be
处理这些被压低的声音。在导言“Read This First”的第 IV 页，
dealing with these toned-down sounds. In the introduction, read this first page IV,
我谈过过度发音。这一节会处理这个问题。
I talked about overpronouncing. This section will handle that
你会轻轻带过一些词，也会省掉
overpronunciation. You're going to skim over words, you're going to through
某些声音。你的峰会很强，但谷会比较模糊。
certain sounds. Your peaks are going to be quite strong, but your valleys blurry. A
这种非常直觉化的语调能力，会通过这些练习逐渐建立起来。
very intuitive aspect of intonation that this practice will help you develop.
the、a 这类冠词通常是非常弱化的声音。
Articles such as the, uh, are usually very reduced sounds. Before a consonant, the
在辅音前，the 和 a 都是弱化的 schwa 音；不过在元音前，
and uh are both schwa sounds, which are reduced. Before a vowel, however, you'll
你会注意到变化。the 的 schwa 会变成长 E 加 Y；the book 会变成
notice a change. The schwa of the turns into a long e plus a Y. The book changes
比如 the only book。a 在元音前会变成 an，例如 an ugly hat。
to thee only book. A hat becomes an ugly hat. The article a becomes an. Think of an
这些例子都用 orange，而不是 an orange。
orange rather than an orange. An opening, an eye, an imaginary animal.